const data = [
  {
    id: 1,
    front: "1",
    back: { value: "4", suit: "C" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    front: "2",
    back: { value: "2", suit: "H" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    front: "3",
    back: { value: "7", suit: "D" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    front: "4",
    back: { value: "3", suit: "C" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    front: "5",
    back: { value: "4", suit: "H" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    front: "6",
    back: { value: "6", suit: "D" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    front: "7",
    back: { value: "A", suit: "S" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    front: "8",
    back: { value: "5", suit: "H" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    front: "9",
    back: { value: "9", suit: "S" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    front: "10",
    back: { value: "2", suit: "S" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    front: "11",
    back: { value: "Q", suit: "H" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    front: "12",
    back: { value: "3", suit: "D" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    front: "13",
    back: { value: "Q", suit: "C" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    front: "14",
    back: { value: "8", suit: "H" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    front: "15",
    back: { value: "6", suit: "S" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    front: "16",
    back: { value: "5", suit: "S" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    front: "17",
    back: { value: "9", suit: "H" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    front: "18",
    back: { value: "K", suit: "C" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    front: "19",
    back: { value: "2", suit: "D" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    front: "20",
    back: { value: "J", suit: "H" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    front: "21",
    back: { value: "3", suit: "S" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    front: "22",
    back: { value: "8", suit: "S" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    front: "23",
    back: { value: "6", suit: "H" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    front: "24",
    back: { value: "T", suit: "C" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    front: "25",
    back: { value: "5", suit: "D" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    front: "26",
    back: { value: "K", suit: "D" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    front: "27",
    back: { value: "2", suit: "C" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    front: "28",
    back: { value: "3", suit: "H" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    front: "29",
    back: { value: "8", suit: "D" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    front: "30",
    back: { value: "5", suit: "C" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 31,
    front: "31",
    back: { value: "K", suit: "S" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 32,
    front: "32",
    back: { value: "J", suit: "D" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 33,
    front: "33",
    back: { value: "8", suit: "C" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 34,
    front: "34",
    back: { value: "T", suit: "S" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 35,
    front: "35",
    back: { value: "K", suit: "H" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 36,
    front: "36",
    back: { value: "J", suit: "C" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 37,
    front: "37",
    back: { value: "7", suit: "S" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 38,
    front: "38",
    back: { value: "T", suit: "H" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 39,
    front: "39",
    back: { value: "A", suit: "D" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 40,
    front: "40",
    back: { value: "4", suit: "S" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 41,
    front: "41",
    back: { value: "7", suit: "H" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 42,
    front: "42",
    back: { value: "4", suit: "D" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 43,
    front: "43",
    back: { value: "A", suit: "C" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 44,
    front: "44",
    back: { value: "9", suit: "C" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 45,
    front: "45",
    back: { value: "J", suit: "S" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 46,
    front: "46",
    back: { value: "Q", suit: "D" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 47,
    front: "47",
    back: { value: "7", suit: "C" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 48,
    front: "48",
    back: { value: "Q", suit: "S" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 49,
    front: "49",
    back: { value: "T", suit: "D" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 50,
    front: "50",
    back: { value: "6", suit: "C" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 51,
    front: "51",
    back: { value: "A", suit: "H" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 52,
    front: "52",
    back: { value: "9", suit: "D" },
    confidence: 0,
  },
];
